{
    "subject": "resource/North_Korea",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/North_Korean_won",
    "human_readable": "The currency of North Korea is North Korean won.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9548898339271545,
            "question": "What type of currency is the North Korean won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.930492103099823,
            "question": "Is the North Korean won a recognized international currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8837499022483826,
            "question": "What is the currency of North Korea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7191524505615234,
            "question": "What are some common denominations of the North Korean won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6999083757400513,
            "question": "How does the value of the North Korean won compare to other currencies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.696083664894104,
            "question": "How is the value of the North Korean won determined?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5362445712089539,
            "question": "What is the name of the monetary unit used in North Korea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4693307876586914,
            "question": "Has the North Korean won undergone any significant revaluations or reforms?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45183616876602173,
            "question": "What factors influence the exchange rate of the North Korean won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42570823431015015,
            "question": "Are there any restrictions on using or exchanging the North Korean won?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of North Korea is North Korean won.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8882_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors influence the exchange rate of the North Korean won?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8882_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has the North Korean won undergone any significant revaluations or reforms?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8882_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the monetary unit used in North Korea?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8882_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8882_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the North Korean Won is the official currency of North Korea (Democratic People's Republic of Korea), supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}